Irma Kalish Scripts and Videos
Irma Kalish Scripts and Videos
- Scripts
  - McKeever and the Colonel
    - Young McKeever Had a Farm (Box 20)
  - Meet Corlis Archer
    - 19B - Costume Party - Final Master Script, 10/25/54 (Box 20)
  - Meet Millie TV
    - 54-24 - Alfred Sues Sr., 8/24/54 (Box 20)
  - Merry Go-Round
    - Presentation (Box 20)
  - Millionaire
    - 367 - Phillip Sargent, 11/3/55 (Box 20)
  - Moose
    - Pilot Script, 2/25/74 (Box 20)
  - My Favorite Martian
    - Two to Get Ready - Revised, 1/7/64 (Box 20)
  - My Three Sons
    - 5272-91 - Tramp's First Bite (Rev. 5/10/62), 5/4/62 (Box 20)
    - 5272-115 - Caged Fury, 9/20/62 (Box 20)
    - 5272-124 - Toupee, 4/30/63 (Box 20)
    - 5272-151 - Fish Gotta Swin - Birds Gotta Fly, 8/23/63 (Box 20)
    - 5272-173 - Uncle Charlie & the Redskins (Rev. 6/24/64), 5/24/64 (Box 20)
    - 5272-182 - Lady in the Air, 7/8/64 (Box 20)
    - Leopard's Spots, 7/28/64 (Box 20)
    - 5272-205 -vDouglas A Go-Go (Rev. 4/29/65, 6/28/65), 4/23/65 (Box 20)
    - 5272-224 - Our Boy in Washington, 8/25/65 (Box 20)
    - 5272-231 - Ernie's Folly, 3/16/66 (Box 20)
    - 5272-248 - Fiddler Under the Roof (Rev. 6/22/66), 5/23/66 (Box 20)
    - 2245-0677 - Honorable Guest, 8/23/67 (Box 20)
    - 2245-0678 - Ernie, the Jinx, 9/7/67 (Box 20)
    - 2245-0770 - Polly, the Pidgeon, 5/10/71 (Box 21)
  - Nanny and the Professor
    - Nanny on Wheels - Final, 12/30/69 (Box 21)
    - Whatever Happened to Felicity? - Final, 6/16/71 (Box 21)
  - Nate
    - Presentation (Box 21)
  - No Vacancy
    - Presentation Notes, 10/15/76 (Box 21)
  - Nobody's Perfect
    - Cookie's Place Segment (Box 21)
  - Oklahoma
    - Rocky Kalish [title on folder but not on script] (Box 21)
  - One for the Road
    - Inter-Office Memo, 1/18/80 (Box 21)
    - Pilot Script - First Draft, 2/22/80; 2 copies (Box 21)
    - Pilot Script - Original First Draft, 2/22/80 (Box 21)
    - Pilot Script - First Draft w/ Notes, 2/22/80 (Box 21)
    - Pilot Script - Revised First Draft, 2/27/80; 4 copies (Box 21)
    - Pilot Script - Original Revised First Draft, 2/27/80 (Box 22)
    - Pilot Script - Revised First Draft w/ Cover Sheet, 2/27/80 (Box 22)
    - Pilot Script - Revised First Draft w/ Notes, 2/27/80 (Box 22)
    - Pilot Script - Second Draft, 3/7/80; 4 copies (Box 22)
  - Out of the Blue
    - Presentation Notes, 3/7/80 (Box 22)
    - Over There, 5/23/79 (Box 22)
  - Petticoat Junction
    - 83344 - Unrest at Shady Rest, 7/7/67 (Box 22)
  - Proposal
    - Proposal for Elizabeth Montgomery, 3/18/64 (Box 22)
  - Rendezvous Hotel
    - Pilot Script - Second Draft, 3/21/78; 2 copies (Box 22)
    - Revised Final Draft, 4/28/78 (Box 22)
  - Rendezvous Lodge
    - Pilot Script (Box 23)
  - Rendezvous Motel
    - Pilot Script, Partial (Box 23)
    - Pilot Script, 3 folders (Box 23)
    - Pilot Script - Second Draft, 3/17/78 (Box 23)
  - Seduction Machine
    - [no title] (Box 23)
  - Skin Deep
    - Pilot Story (Box 23)
    - Pilot Script (Box 24)
    - Presentation (Box 24)
  - Smith Family
    - 8044-0607 - Remember Lisa - First Draft, 9/11/70 (Box 24)
    - 8044-0615 - Peer Group - First Draft, 11/6/70 (Box 24)
    - 8044-0620 - Rogue Cop, 5/5/71-9/14/71; multiple drafts and revisions (Box 24)
    - 8044-0625 - Blind Chance, 5/13/71-6/22/71; multiple drafts and revisions (Box 24)
    - 8044-0630 - San Francisco Cop - First Draft, 6/29/71 (Box 24)
    - 8044-0640 - Man in the Middle - First Draft, 9/1/71 (Box 24)
  - Sugar & Spice
    See also Videos: Sugar & Spice, below.
    - 0101 - Pilot Script, 9/30/89 (Box 24)
    - 0102 - Breaking In is Hard to Do - Tape Script, 12/8/89 (Box 24)
    - 0103 - This Hostess Ain't No Cupcake - Tape Day Script, 12/14/89 (Box 24)
    - 0104 - Truck Stops Here - Tape Script, 1/11/90 (Box 24)
    - 0105 - Doo-Wah Ditty in Ponca City - Tape Script, 1/18/90 (Box 24)
    - 0106 - A Star is Boring - Tape Script, 1/25/90 (Box 24)
    - 0107 - Lovers and Other Truckers - Tape Script, 2/8/90 (Box 24)
  - Supercops
    - Cleanout, 8/30/74 (Box 24)
    - Cleanout, 9/12/74 (Box 24)
    - The Grey Guard - Revised, 12/23/74 (Box 24)
    - Fence - Revised, 3/11/75 (Box 24)
  - Tabitha
    - 183148 - Boy Gets Witch - Revised Draft, 1/19/76 (Box 25)
  - To Rome With Love
    - 2928-0523 - West of Rome, 11/28/69; 12/4/69,; 1/6/70 (Box 25)
    - 2928-0524 - Spring Vacation, 12/18/69; 12/22/69,; 1/22/70 (Box 25)
    - 2928-0532 - Runaways - First Draft, 5/19/70 (Box 25)
  - Too Close for Comfort
    - 81-205 - Where There's a Will - Final Draft, 8/27/81 (Box 25)
    - 81-222 - A Policeman's Wife is Not a Happy One - Final Draft, 2/12/82 (Box 25)
  - US
    - Series Presentation (Box 25)
    - Working Script (Box 25)
    - Pilot Story (Box 25)
    - Pilot Script - Second Draft, 10/7/77; 2 copies (Box 25)
    - Series of Presentations (Box 25)
  - Wilder & Wilder (His & Hers & Hers)
    - Pilot Script - Final Draft w/ Production Notes, 3/31/78 (Box 25)
    - Pilot Script - Final Draft, 3/31/78 (Box 26)
  - Women in Communications, Inc.
    - Memo & Newsletter, 4/7/82 (Box 26)
  - Zack
    See also Hannibal (alternate title: The Making of the Mayor).
    - Making of the Mayor - Pilot Script - Second Draft, 1/16/84; 3 copies (Box 26)
  - Unidentified
    - Unidentified script (Box 26)
- Videos
  - 227
    - Episodes 501, 502, 503, 504, 1989; kalish_001; 1 VHS tape (Oversize 1)
      Episode 501, The Flight of the Century; Episode 502, A Pampered Tale; Episode 503, Take My Diva - Please; Episode 504, Tenants, Anyone?
    - Episodes 505, 506, 507, 508, 1989; kalish_002; 1 VHS tape (Oversize 1)
      Episode 505, [no title]; Episode 506, How the West Was Fun Part II; Episode 507, There Go The Clowns; Episode 508, War is Heck
    - Episodes 509, 510, 511, 512, 1989; kalish_003; 1 VHS tape (Oversize 1)
      Episode 509, Flying Down to Leo's; Episode 510, Video-Activity; Episode 511, Reunion Blues; Episode 512, The Perfume Game
    - Episodes 513, 514, 515, 516, 1989; kalish_004; 1 VHS tape (Oversize 1)
      Episode 513, Gone Fishing; Episode 514, Come the Revolution; Episode 515, Guess Who's Not Coming to Christmas; Episode 516, Where Do We Go From Here
    - Episodes 517, 518, 519, 520, 1990; kalish_005; 1 VHS tape (Oversize 1)
      Episode 517, Knock it Off; Episode 518, You Gotta Have Art; Episode 519, Do Not Pass Go (Part I); Episode 520, Do Not Pass Go (Part II)
    - Episode 523, Nightmare on 227, 3/21/90; kalish_006; 1 VHS tape (Oversize 1)
  - Hogan Family
    - 446351 - California Dreamin' Part I - Final, 9/13/90; kalish_007; 1 VHS tape (Oversize 1)
    - 446352 - California Dreamin' Part II - Final Sweetened Version, 9/20/90; kalish_008; 1 VHS tape (Oversize 1)
    - 446353 - The Plays the Thing - Final Sweetened Version, 10/4/90; kalish_009; 1 VHS tape (Oversize 1)
    - 446354 - Baby Stops Here - Final Sweetened Version, 9/27/90; kalish_010; 1 VHS tape (Oversize 1)
    - 446355 - From Russia with Fries - Final Sweetened Version, 10/9/90; kalish_011; 1 VHS tape (Oversize 1)
    - 446356 - X Marks the Spot - Final Sweetened Version, 10/18/90; kalish_012; 1 VHS tape (Oversize 1)
    - 446358 - Best of Friends, Worst of Times - Final Sweetened Version, 11/1/90; kalish_013; 1 VHS tape (Oversize 1)
    - 446359 - Come Fly with Me - Final Sweetened Version, 11/7/90; kalish_014; 1 VHS tape (Oversize 1)
    - 446360 - Sneaking Suspicion - Final Sweetened Version, 11/14/90; kalish_015; 1 VHS tape (Oversize 1)
    - 446361 - Ho, Ho, Hogan - Final, 12/5/90; kalish_016; 1 VHS tape (Oversize 1)
    - 446363 - Isn't it Romantic - Final, 12/19/90; kalish_017; 1 VHS tape (Oversize 1)
  - Sugar & Spice
    - 101 - Pilot, 10/19/89; kalish_018; 1 VHS tape (Oversize 1)
    - 101 - Revised Pilot, 2/27/90; kalish_019; 1 VHS tape (Oversize 1)
    - 102 - [no title], [1990]; kalish_020; 1 VHS tape (Oversize 1)
    - 103 - [no title], [1990]; kalish_021; 1 VHS tape (Oversize 1)
    - 104 - Truck Stops Here, 1/26/90; kalish_022; 1 VHS tape (Oversize 1)
    - 105 - Doo-Wah Ditty in Ponca City, 2/16/90; kalish_023; 1 VHS tape (Oversize 1)
    - 106 - A Star is Boring, 2/20/90; kalish_024; 1 VHS tape (Oversize 1)
    - 107 - Lovers and Other Truckers, 2/27/90; kalish_025; 1 VHS tape (Oversize 1)